http://www.meals-on-wheels.org/privacy-policy

Main menu
Get MealsMonthly MenuEventsDonateDonate - 2020 Holiday CardFund a SeniorDonate a VehicleDonate In-Kind and/or Auction ItemsVia WIlls/BequestsGive StockVolunteerIndividuals and FamiliesGroups and BusinessesFAQsOur StoriesMESSAGE FROM PRESIDENT & CEO Metamorphosis Once AgainShare Your StoryLeadershipBoard of Trustees
Enter Zip-code below *
You are hereHome Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Non-Discrimination Policy Statement for Programs and ServicesMeals on Wheels San Diego County, has a policy of non-discrimination in all programs and services. No one shall be excluded on the basis of race, color, national origin, sex, sexual orientation, religion, age, marital status, veteran and military status or disability unless required by the eligibility guidelines for services.
Donor Privacy PolicyMeals on Wheels San Diego County does not sell or distribute donor information in any way. You can be assured your information is secured and protected at all times and only used by this agency in processing your donation and supplying you with Meals on Wheels San Diego County information.
PayforMeals
Current MenuPay for Meals
2254 San Diego Ave, Suite 200San Diego, California 92110Phone: 619-260-6110Fax: 619-267-6373Regional office locations click HERE1.800.5.SENIOR
Privacy Policy
© 2020 Meals on Wheels San Diego County. All Rights Reserved.Website by: OneEach Technologies
Meals on Wheels San Diego County is a 501(c)(3) nonprofit recognized by the IRS
|
Number 95-2660509
